复习练习 1-38：动词时态变化中保持名词重音。
Review exercise 138 consistent noun stress and changing verb tenses One the floods
erode the mountains Two the floods eroded the mountains Three the floods are eroding
the mountains Four the floods will erode the mountains Five the floods that erode
the mountains Six the floods that have eroded the mountains 7. The floods that
have eroded the mountains. 8. The floods that have eroded the mountains. 9. The
floods that have eroded the mountains. 10. The floods that have eroded the mountains.
11. The floods that erode the mountains. 12. The floods that should erode the
mountains. 13. The floods that shouldn't erode the mountains. 14, the flood should
have eroded the mountains. 15, the flood shouldn't have eroded the mountains. 16,
the floods could erode the mountains. 17, the floods couldn't erode the mountains.
18, the floods could have eroded the mountains. 19, the floods couldn't have
eroded the mountains. 20, the floods might erode the mountains. 21. The floods might
have eroded the mountains. 22. The floods must erode the mountains. 23. The floods
must have eroded the mountains. 24. The floods can erode the mountains. 25. The
floods can't erode the mountains.